PAUL DANIEL ILIES

paul.ilies@hotmail.com

Str. Florilor no.188 Floresti, Cluj Corporation of the corporation o

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

An aspiring **junior software developer** with 2 years of experience in **front-end development** (self-learning), graduated the postgraduate program in **Applied Informatics and Programming** at Technical University of Cluj-Napoca in 2021. Learning the basics of programming in **C++**, relational databases with **Oracle SQL**, web technologies as **HTML**, **CSS**, **Javascript**, **React**, programming in **C#**, the bases of computer systems and networks, **Object Oriented Programming** concepts and fundamental algoritms (binary search, bubble sort, insertion sort).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SELF LEARNING October 2019 – Present

I graduated the postgraduate program in Applied Informatics and Programming (4 semesters) at Technical University from Cluj-Napoca and self-learned the Front-end Developer path: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, REDUX, NODEJS, EXPRESS, MONGODB

Front-end Developer

Accumulating knowledge by creating personal projects with technologies mentioned above.

- Bread Dough Calculator: Project built with React, React Bootstrap, NodeJS, Express and MongoDB.
- TaskApp: Project built with React, Redux, NodeJs, Express, MongoDB, raw CSS.
- Portfolio: Project built with React, raw CSS, NodeJS, Express.

PREVIOUS ROLES

Operations Analyst/TEREOS (December 2020 – Present (redundacy process))

Financial Analyst/ CMIE ROMANIA (December 2018- September 2020 (I was made redundant))

Operations Analyst/Sports Operator/ BETFAIR ROMANIA (August 2017- September 2018)

Operations Global Executive/STA TRAVEL (2017)

Receptionist/ HOSPITALITY (2006-2017)

EDUCATION

Continuous Education - Applied Informatics and programming- Technical University (2019-2021) **Economics-** Romanian American University of Bucharest (2004-2008)

OTHER RELEVANT INFORMATION

Languages: English (Intermediate), Italian (Elementary)

Computer skills: Word (advanced), Excel (advanced (pivot tables, vlookup's))

Programming: Html, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, C++(begginer), SQL